yumedeals.com 2015-06-30

# Privacy Policy

**SELECTION**

Protecting your privacy is very important to us. We have accordingly developed this Privacy Policy to protect your personal information and keep it confidential. We do everything we reasonably can to protect your rights of privacy on systems and the Website controlled by us, “Yumedeals” may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 19th

**WHAT WE COLLECT**

1.We may collect the following information

2.Name and job title

3.Contact information including email address

4.Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests

5.Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION GATHER**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

1.Internal record keeping.

2.We may use the information to improve our products and services.

3.We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may f  find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

4.From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by      email, phone, fax or mail.

5.We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

6.We may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes.

7.We will never sell your information

**SECURITY**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**RIGHT TO COLLECT**

By accepting the Terms of Service you agree that we may collect and store your Personal Information as long as you use our Services subject to the limitations set out in this Privacy Policy.  
2.1 We collect your Profiling and Account Information for the following reasons:  
(a) We need your identity details, contact details, banking information and account history to manage our relationship with you and provide Services to you. We may use this information for suggesting products and promotional offers and schemes. We will only disclose this information as provided below.  
(b) We use certain of your information in an aggregated form to compile statistical and demographical profiles for our business and marketing activities. We may disclose such information about you, provided that the information is in an aggregated form that is not capable of being used or interpreted in such a manner as to identify you.  
2.2 We collect and store your Service Usage and Transactional Information to:  
(a) determine and verify the Service Charges payable by you and to administer our relationship with you.  
(b) comply with any statutory or regulatory requirement.  
(c) compile statistical and demographical profiles about you for our business and marketing activities and to customise our Services to you. While we are entitled to use such information about you for our own internal business purposes without limitation, we will only disclose it in an aggregated form which is not capable of being used or interpreted in such a manner as to identify you; and  
(d) monitor your use of our Services for the purposes of ensuring compliance with our Terms of Service.  
2.3 We collect and store your Correspondence Information and Personal Identifiers to:  
(a) comply with our obligations under law; and  
(b) monitor your use of our Services in order to ensure your compliance with our Terms of Service. Any Personal Information which we collect and which we may use in an aggregated format ensuring you are not individually identified is our property. We may use it, in our sole discretion and without any compensation to you, for any legitimate purpose including (without limitation) the commercial sale thereof to third parties. Sometime we use “cookies” so that we can provide you with more customised information when you return to our website. “Cookies” are used to store user preferences and to track user trends, so as to enhance your interactive experience and generally improve our Services to you. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a “cookie”, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. If you do accept a “cookie”, you thereby agree to our use of any Personal Information collected by us using that Cookie. You may update your Profiling Information at any time on the website. You acknowledge and agree that in the interests of improving personalization and Service efficiency, we may, under controlled and secure circumstances, share your Personal Information with our affiliates (an entity which is our subsidiary or holding company or a subsidiary of our holding company or an entity which controls, is controlled by or is under common control with us).
